Daniel Doherty

Full-Stack Developer

518.221.2857

About

I am a full-stack web developer, I navigate seamlessly between creativity, logic, and organization. I have worked in distribution, customer service, bicycle sales and repair. I am hard-working and a quick-learner, I have an analytical mind and welcome the opportunity to think pragmatically in order to solve any problem given to me. I hope we can work together someday soon!

Experience

East Side King

Cook

February 2016 - February 2017

Austin, TX

At this high-volume, fast-paced, and well-regarded eatery, I was forced to learn quickly and under pressure. I learned the value of working closely with a team and at times took on a leadership role.

Natural Choice Distribution

Driver

February 2015 - December 2015

Oakland, CA

This growing distribution company has it's driver's not only deliver the product, but also do inventory, merchandising, and sales.

Bikes 4 Life

Bicycle Mechanic

February 2011 - April 2015

Oakland, CA

I helped to develop this popular non-profit. I worked tirelessly, not only as a bicycle mechanic, but as a community outreach and volunteer coordinator.

Education

General Assembly

Web Development Immersive

February 2017 - May 2017

Austin, TX

SUNY Albany

Philosophy

August 2004 - June 2007

Albany, NY

Skills

Front End: HTML5 - CSS - Javascript - jQuery - ReactJs - React

Native - Redux - AngularJs - AJAX

Backend: NodeJs - ExpressJS - NoSQL - RESTful API - Auth

Other: Git - Firebase - Java - Python